https://warplaylasertag.com/privacy-policy/

Private Games
What is our Military Grade Laser Tag?
Private Games
What is our Military Grade Laser Tag?
Private Games
What is our Military Grade Laser Tag?
Private Games
What is our Military Grade Laser Tag?
Make a Reservation
Videos
Wavier
Contact
Due to the recent events and limits on large gatherings, we offer small family private outdoor games during the week and weekend. Call for details.
Website Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. The information below sets the how we use and protect any information that you give our company when you use this website. If you provide us with any information in which you can be identified, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are agreeing to use this website, knowing the current privacy policy.1) We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.2) We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it or you want something from us that requires this information (ie, contact us or any other form in which you are requesting something from us.)3) We don’t sell any information that we do collect. That information is received for our company and the purpose in doing business with our customers, unless required by law to do so.4) If you do give us your personal information, then you may receive, from time to time, communications about our product or services through promotional marketing, via e-mail, phone, fax or mail. At any time, you may request that we don’t contact you for any other purposes and can do so by contacting us direct through our contact us information on this website or contacting us direct by phone at the number listed on our website.Website VisitorsLike more websites, we collect non-personal-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, location of IP address, referring site, search term in which we were found and the date and time of each visitor request. This information is available and is used to better understand how our visitor’s use our website. From time to time, this information may be available and reviewed by us or our webmaster, and may release non-personal-identifying information in the aggregate, for example publishing information on current trends in the usage of the website, either in whole, or in combination with other websites.How We Use CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Cookies are used to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of the website, and their website access preferences. Cookies also allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. Web applications can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website and it could prevent some features from working correctly.Business TransfersIf we were to be acquired or be sold, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy or any changes they may choose to make.Links to Other WebsitesOur website may contain links to other websites. However, once you have used these links, you should note that we do not have control over the other website and their privacy policies. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide while visiting such sites and this privacy statement does not govern such sites. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.AdsAds appearing on our website, either today or at any time in the future may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by our company and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertiser’s ads running on our network.We have tried to make this information as easy to read as possible. If you have any questions about any of this information, contact us online and we will get back to you with answers to any question you may have. If you are unsure about the information, you may want to not use our website until you are clear and understand our privacy policies.
Contact Us
Name
Phone
Email
Questions
Submit
571-442-4291
Saturday and Sunday 10:00 AM – 4:00 PM
Private games available during the week with reservations.
What is our Military Grade Laser Tag?
What is our Military Grade Laser Tag?
© 2020, War Play Laser Tag. All Rights Reserved.
